Found under the base of Buddha statue.
You go tell the village headman.
He'll definitely meet me.
The two of us intend to adpot the child right?
Maybe Chanjao's mom was telling the truth.
Maybe it's a true story.
Hello
Grandmother
Cute right?
Regardless of how you love and care.
She's not your own blood.
I warned with good intention.
Are you forgetting it?
You was the one who urged us to go and get the child.
I'm scared you'll be naughty at school and wound.
If you can take care of yourself then you can go.
Are you very naughty?
A little bit.
Mother
Old lady this is just a lesson.
Considered very lucky.
That the internal organs of the patient
are not affected at all.
The lungs are normal.
Are you sure that the check has already been completed?
Yes.
So why when I came to the hospital?
Why can't I breath?
Maybe it's because of stress and muscles so it can be tense.
But now you're easy to breathe right?
It's okay mother.
Now we are in the hospital.
Even if there is anything wrong
you don't have to be afraid.
Also tonight I'll be here with you.
Excuse me first.
Thank you.
And are you fine?
Yes mother.
Considered very lucky.
Normally she's easily bruised.
But this is fine.
How is it possible?
She didn't tight like a seat belt.
Didn't you feel some abnormalities?
Considered luck to help you.
You're as lucky as the doctor said.
I'll go back to collect things at home first.
In order to hurry back to be with you.
Let's go.
Say goodnight to Grandma.
Goodnight Grandma.
Get well soon.
I'll hurry to go back.
Mother.
Who are you waiting for?
Do you make an appointment to wash the pool today?
Are you forgetting it?
I've an appointment
so I postpone the mechanic tomorrow instead.
Oh yes. I forgot.
I'll finish the business for about two o'clock in the afternoon.
If you want anything please call.
Excuse me.
This kid?
Yes
It has a spirit.
Who's the spirit?
A woman.
Or whether it is her mother?
Can't see it clearly.
Like something is covering.
It's not normal.
If not hurry to take her away.
This house will definitely disappear.
Then...
So what should I do?
Hey!
Sir
Don't mess with her.
Sir.
Wait
Sir
Sir wait sir.
Sir.
Wait.
At this edge
Why is this so cruel?
Dao
What clip do you watch? It's noisy.
Accident clip A father reverses his car
and runs over his own child. It's terrifying.
Would you like to watch?
Crazy?
Mental disorder.
Which color will you take?
You can get red here.
And here?
- Orange
- Orange gradient right?
Very beautiful.
Will change to red?
Then it's red.
Y 100 and M 100?
Yes
Mother
Can I go to play at the garden?
Oh okay.
So I'll hurry to fix and then hurry to send as soon as possible.
Yes
Uh Dao go tell the technician
that the money has been transferred.
Here it's under the car.
Do.
I'll give money to you tomorrow.
Sure?
Yes sure.
That's it.
Yeah that's it.
Can you see it?
That's it.
Hey!
Oh my!
Khun Chanjao
Chanjao
Gradually come out and come out.
Be careful.
Oh
Why did you go in?
So naughty.
Next time don't get in.
She said that you asked her to pick up the earrings.
She talked nonsense.
I didn't say that.
But she is not a liar.
Hey are you saying I'm a liar?
Yes!
Now if I've no meaning in this house.
If you worship it so much then put it on a pedestal and worship
it bowing down to its feet and bowing in reverence.
So...
Who are you?
Sigh.
It's hurt.
Saying anything no one believes.
Crazy girl.
Hey!
Ouch!
Give me the ring.
Don't do anything to me. I'll give you all.
Here.
Hurry
Ouch it's hurt.
Why did you hit me?
Ouch!
Ah
Don't do anything.
Ploy
She has to go.
Mother
Are you going to eat?
I'm not hungry yet.
Let's go outside first.
I'll follow you.
She died because of me.
Hey
It's not your fault.
Hmm.
If not because I spoke badly to the mother.
It wouldn't be like this.
Mother
Is that you?
I'm sorry.
I...
It's my fault.
Please forgive me.
Mother
I apologize.
Oh
Mother mother don't
Mother
Ploy
Calm down.
Ploy what's wrong?
Ploy
A nightmare?
Aside from medicine and group activities.
If possible I encourages you to change environment.
Avoid going to places that bring up negative memories.
Go to find a place to be happy.
So you don't have to think about the past.
Then I will pay first.
Dan thank you very much.
Take Ploy to travel to Songkhla.
Or if you can help with my work it is even better
Next semester there are many teachers to go to study.
Yes.
Dan
You had said that you wanted me to help teaching.
Is it still lacking of teacher?
I'm here.
You can follow the map.
Sorry that I didn't go to pick up.
There is an urgent seminar.
Oh it's fine.
I thank you very much for helping me.
Hey it's fine.
After finishing the work I'll call you.
Yes bro.
I think we should call Dan.
There is no phone signal.
Sigh.
This is like coming to the same place.
We didn't go through here.
If you see a house I'll go down and ask.
That woman.
Where is the women?
A woman standing in a spooky lonely place
But I really saw her.
Before reaching the three-way intersection I saw her.
If you see her again tell me.
I will go down to ask the way.
There shouldn't have any people.
They have.
I see you've already walked into the house.
Oh wait here.
I'll ask.
Thep
Don't go.
You wait here with Chanjao.
Please come back.
Father come back.
Thep
What are you doing here?
The lady ask for you.
Who are you looking for?
Someone I know.
Who? What's his name?
I just knew her yesterday.
Not yet asked the name.
I don't know how she is here.
Probably a guest of Khun Luang.
Or the lady.
Let's go.
The lady is waiting.
Thep Where have you been?
Pay respect to your uncle and aunt.
Now your uncle has become the governor.
What are you prostrating to?
Thep is a student from abroad.
Shouldn't they have to check their hands?
I would like to pay respect to you.
- Yes
If we meet elsewhere I may can't remember you.
Last time we met
When you went to study in Phra Nakhon.
At that time it should be about 11 years old.
This has been 11 years ago.
At that time he was looks good.
Now he's a young man.
As handsome as an angel.
Really elegant.
Oh and what did you study in France?
Political science.
I will ask you to work at the Ministry of Foreign Affairs.
Good.
You'll will definitely be the Chancellor in the future.
Unfortunately
Here if our daughter is still single
I will ask him for married her.
How about our grandchildren?
My grandchildren are now 2 years old.
Sir
He couldn't wait.
Oh a little.
Can't be.
Still hurt?
A little wound.
Looking for someone?
It's Kem
Let he go other place.
Friends have all the wives.
Oh my mother.
Here we are the same.
I will find the girls for you to know.
Oh Thep.
Now there is a female Nora dancer in our neighborhood.
Can a woman dance Nora?
Who would think that...
Norajiam's daughter used to come and pick mangosteens
at the end of the orchard.
Will become a famous Nora.
How is the hand?
It's better.
Can you remember me?
I'm glad to see you again.
Have you finished?
I'm done dad
How do you know him?
This person took me to the doctor.
This is the person I've looked for.
How do you know her?
Is the name Buanga?
Yesterday when I went out to drive.
I saw her a bike falling.
And when she was going to see a doctor.
So I volunteered to take her.
Doctor
Can you help?
The sewing needle is stuck in my hand
but I don't know why.
The bleeding does not stop.
This way please.
Thepparit
Somkid
I intend to wait for you until the wound is done.
But I just met an old friend
who invited to eat drink a coffee.
When coming back again I didn't see her anymore.
Kem
Yes sir.
Do you know Buanga's house?
I doubt they would go outside.
Shall we come next day?
Chanjao
Stay in the car do not go anywhere.
Do you understand?
Up the mirror.
Do not go anywhere. I'll be back.
Oh
Thep
Ploy
We should hurriedly get out of here first.
Let's go.
Thep
OK what happened?
I can't think of it.
I just walked in there.
No one is in the house.
And when I opened my eyes again.
I see you.
Chanjao
- Chanjao
- Ouch.
Ploy
Thep
Chanjao
She was really coming.
And look at her outfit.
Poor and not modest.
Be disgusting.
Do you have any problems?
The room that my seniors booked.
Someone has stayed.
Well that woman.
She just checked in half an hour ago.
This is Luang Decha Adireksorn.
He's my great -grandfather.
The first day I took you to be difficult.
Nevermind.
Being busy is good too.
I won't have time to think too much.